A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 3, Series 15 FA1485
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants and Program Files, 1982-2012; 1
  - Harvard University - Reede (20020651) - Fellowship in Minority Health Policy: Support for Program Direction and Fellowships, 2003-2004, 2002-2004 (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Cooper (20010108) (Box 63, Folder 3-5)
  - AcademyHealth - Marian Mankin (20030488) (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Fairbrother (2002023) - How Internists are Coping with their Uninsured Caseloads (Box 64, Folder 2-3)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Fairbrother (2002023) - How Internists are Coping with their Uninsured Caseloads - Grant Products (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Association of Academic Health Centers - Evans (20020763) (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Association of Academic Health Centers - Evans (20020763) (Box 65, Folder 1-2)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - Turnbull (20020724), 2002-2006 (Box 65, Folder 3-4)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - Turnbull (20020724), 2002-2006 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - United Hospital Fund (980184) - Medicare Managed Care (Box 66, Folder 2-4)
  - Harvard (980753) - Quality of Care Within Medicaid Managed Care Plans (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Harvard (980753) - Quality of Care Within Medicaid Managed Care Plans (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Robbett, Rosenthal and Jennings (20010101) - Public Education Campaign, Medicaid Enrollment in New York City (Box 67, Folder 2-4)
  - Robbett, Rosenthal and Jennings (20010101) - Public Education Campaign, Medicaid Enrollment in New York City (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Robbett, Rosenthal and Jennings (20010101) - Public Education Campaign, Medicaid Enrollment in New York City - Original Subway Ads, 2015:036:002 (Roll 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Poster
  - Urban Institute - Moon (20010103) (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Covering Kids Meeting, 2000 September 19 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Center for Budget and Policy Priorities (20010157) (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), Institute of Medicine (IOM) (20000043) (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - New York Lawyers for Public Interest, Inc. (2000440) - Commission on the Public Health System in New York City (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Center on Budget and Policy Priorities - Mann (990655), 1999 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Gray, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Nuffield Trust (20000048) - Leatherman, 1999-2000 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Barondess (990936), 1999-2000 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - New York University (NYU) - Wagner Dialogues (990916) (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - American Accreditation HealthCare Commission (990498) - Greenberg, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - New York Public Library - Fisher (20000799), 2000-2001 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Greater New York Hospital Association (20000758) (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), Institute of Medicine (IOM) (980719) (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - National Committee for Quality Health Care - McDermott, 1999-2002 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Child Defense Fund - Dutton (990334), 1999-2000 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Harvard Medical School - McNeil (980776) - Quality of Cardiac Care Provided by Managed Medical Groups, 1998-2006 (Box 70, Folder 2-3)
  - Harvard Medical School - McNeil (980776) - Quality of Cardiac Care Provided by Managed Medical Groups - Proposal Development, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Harvard Medical School - McNeil (980776) - Quality of Cardiac Care Provided by Managed Medical Groups - Administration and Background, 1998-2002 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Harvard Medical School - McNeil (980776) - Quality of Cardiac Care Provided by Managed Medical Groups - Correspondence, 2000-2002 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Harvard Medical School - McNeil (980776) - Quality of Cardiac Care Provided by Managed Medical Groups - Grant Products, 1998-2003 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Thomas Jefferson University - Nash (20020184) - Health Care Quality Improvements, 2001-2006 (Box 71, Folder 3-4)
  - Thomas Jefferson University - Nash (20020184) - Health Care Quality Improvements - Grant Products (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Thomas Jefferson University - Nash (20020184) - Health Care Quality Improvements (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Thomas Jefferson University - Nash (20020184) - Health Care Quality Improvements - Articles and Background (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Health Research and Educational Trust (HRET) - Pittman (20010573) - Reducing Medication Errors and Improving Patient Safety in U.S. Hospitals (Box 72, Folder 3-5)
  - Health Research and Educational Trust (HRET) - Pittman (20010573) - Reducing Medication Errors and Improving Patient Safety in U.S. Hospitals - Proposal Development (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Health Research and Educational Trust (HRET) - Pittman (20010573) - Reducing Medication Errors and Improving Patient Safety in U.S. Hospitals - Grant Products, 2001-2003 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Johns Hopkins University - School of Hygiene and Public Health - Kasper (94-52) - Care Giving to Disabled Women, 1994-2008 (Box 85, Folder 1-4)
  - Johns Hopkins University - School of Hygiene and Public Health - Kasper (94-52) - Care Giving to Disabled Women - Administration and Budget, 1993-1998 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Johns Hopkins University - School of Hygiene and Public Health - Kasper (94-52) - Care Giving to Disabled Women - Proposal, 1993 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Johns Hopkins University - School of Hygiene and Public Health - Kasper (94-52) - Care Giving to Disabled Women - Correspondence, 1994-2000 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Johns Hopkins University - School of Hygiene and Public Health - Kasper (94-52) - Care Giving to Disabled Women - Grant Products, 1994-2001 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Institute for Health Care Improvement (IHI), National Initiative for Children's Healthcare Quality (NICHQ) (20000800) - Improving the Delivery of Developmental and Behavioral Services in Community Health Centers: Planning (Box 86, Folder 3-5)
  - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Jensen (20010776) - Promoting Healthy Child Development, 2001-2006 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Public Health - Guyer (20010078) - Long-Term Follow-Up of Healthy Steps Families, 2000-2006 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Public Health - Guyer (20010683, 20010078) - Long-Term Follow-Up of Healthy Steps Families - Administration and Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Public Health - Guyer (20010683) - Long-Term Follow-Up of Healthy Steps Families - Proposal, 2000-2001 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Public Health - Guyer (20010078) - Long-Term Follow-Up of Healthy Steps Families - Proposal, 2000-2001 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Public Health - Guyer (20010683) - Long-Term Follow-Up of Healthy Steps Families - Grant Products, 2001-2002 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Public Health - Guyer (20010078) - Long-Term Follow-Up of Healthy Steps Families - Grant Products (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Public Health - Guyer (20010078) - Long-Term Follow-Up of Healthy Steps Families - Grant Products, 2000 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - UCLA - Halfon (970654) - Analysis of Commonwealth Survey of Parents With Young Children (Healthy Steps), 1997-2004 (Box 88, Folder 2-5)
  - UCLA - Halfon (970654) - Analysis of Commonwealth Survey of Parents With Young Children (Healthy Steps), 1997-2004 (Box 89, Folder 1-4)
  - UCLA - Halfon (970654) - Analysis of Commonwealth Survey of Parents With Young Children (Healthy Steps), 1997-2004 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - UCLA - Halfon (980562) - Pediatric Development Project, 1998-2000 (Box 90, Folder 2-3)
  - UCLA - Halfon (970654) - Analysis of Commonwealth Survey of Parents With Young Children (Healthy Steps) - Grant Products, 1997 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - UCLA - Halfon (970654) - Analysis of Commonwealth Survey of Parents With Young Children (Healthy Steps) - Correspondence, 1997-2002 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Northwestern University - Budetti (990565) - Improving the Quality of Health Care Services - Support for Program Direction and Analysis, 1999-2000 (Box 91, Folder 2-3)
  - Northwestern University - Budetti (990565) - Improving the Quality of Health Care Services - Support for Program Direction and Analysis - Administration, 1999-2000 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Northwestern University - Budetti (990565) - Improving the Quality of Health Care Services - Support for Program Direction and Analysis - Proposal Development, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Northwestern University - Budetti (990565) - Improving the Quality of Health Care Services - Support for Program Direction and Analysis - Issue Brief, 1999-2000 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Northwestern University - Budetti (990565) - Improving the Quality of Health Care Services - Support for Program Direction and Analysis - Grant Products, 1999-2000 (Box 92, Folder 2-3)
  - Northwestern University - Budetti (20000509) - Assuring Better Child Health and Development Program (ABCD) - Support for Program Direction and Analysis, 2000-2003 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Northwestern University - Budetti (20000509) - Assuring Better Child Health and Development Program (ABCD) - Support for Program Direction and Analysis - Administration, 2000-2003 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Northwestern University - Budetti (20000509) - Assuring Better Child Health and Development Program (ABCD) - Support for Program Direction and Analysis - Grant Products, 2001-2002 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Northwestern University - Budetti (20000509) - Assuring Better Child Health and Development Program (ABCD) - Support for Program Direction and Analysis - Grant Products, 2000-2001 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Northwestern University - Budetti (20000509) - Assuring Better Child Health and Development Program (ABCD) - Support for Program Direction and Analysis - Proposal Development (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Association of Maternal and Child Health Programs (AMCHP) - Bailey (20030429) - Effective Partnerships Between Title V and Medicaid (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Economic and Social Research Institute - Meyer (20000441) (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Economic and Social Research Institute - Meyer (20000441) - Grant Products, 2001 (Box 94, Folder 1-3)
  - The Lewin Group - 20-20 Vision Project (20000863), 2000-2001 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Economic and Social Research Institute - Meyer (20000863) - Development of A Health Insurance Website, 2000-2002 (Box 95, Folder 1-3)
  - George Washington University - Lambrew (20000863) - Expanding Health Insurance, 2001-2003 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Shikles (20000863), 2000-2002 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - AcademyHealth - Helms (20000863) - State Flexibility to Expand Health Coverage, 2001-2003 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Rutgers University (20000863) - Comprehensive State Strategies for Health Coverage Expansion: New Jersey Case Study, 2000-2002 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Actors' Fund of America - Beaudoin - Support for Improving the Artists' Health Resource Center, 2001-2003 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Johns Hopkins University - School of Public Health - Guyer (20010063) - Healthy Steps National Evaluation (Box 96, Folder 4-5)
  - Healthy Steps Team Meeting, 2001 June 13 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Johns Hopkins University - School of Public Health - Guyer (20010063) - Healthy Steps National Evaluation - Grant Products (Box 97, Folder 1-2)
  - Harvard Medical School - Reede (20010680) - Commonwealth Fund-Harvard Fellowship in Minority Health Policy, 2001-2003 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Harvard Medical School - Reede (20010680) - Commonwealth Fund-Harvard Fellowship in Minority Health Policy - Grant Products, 2002-2003 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Harvard Medical School - Reede (20010680) - Commonwealth Fund-Harvard Fellowship in Minority Health Policy - Grant Products, 2003 (Box 98, Folder 1-3)
  - Health Research and Educational Trust (HRET) - Pittman (20020013) - Eliminating Disparities Through Provider and Community Partnership, 2001-2002 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - National Hispanic Medical Association (NHMA) - Rios (20020059) - Reducing Health Insurance Barriers and Improving Quality of Care for Hispanic Populations (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - National Hispanic Medical Association (NHMA) - Rios (20020059) - Reducing Health Insurance Barriers and Improving Quality of Care for Hispanic Populations, 2002-2004 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - National Hispanic Medical Association (NHMA) - Commonwealth Fund Symposiums (Box 99, Folder 2-4)
  - Small Grants 1993-1997 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Small Grants 1994-1999 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Effective Clinical Practices in Managed Care: Ten Case Studies (980471), 2000 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Small Grants 1998-2000 (Box 100, Folder 3-4)
  - Georgetown Medical Center - Gaskin (96963) (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Weissman (990831) - Quality of Care in Academic Health Centers (AHCs), 1999-2002 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Small Grants 1998-2001 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Center for Health Care Policy and Evaluation (990771), 2001-2003 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - American Association of Homes and Services for the Aging (20000483) - Frail Elders Program, 2000-2002 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - Leape (990557) - Physician and Medical Error, 1999-2001 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - FACCT - Lansky (20010529 PDF) - Policy Paper on Quality Information in Incremental Health Reform, 2001-2002 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - FACCT - Lansky (20010529 PDF) - Policy Paper on Quality Information in Incremental Health Reform, 2001-2002 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - AARP Foundation - Dubow (20031242) - Feasibility of Developing A Model Physician Directory for Medicare Beneficiaries, 2003-2004 (Box 102, Folder 2-4)
  - State of Washington Department of Social and Health Services - Wilson (20010465), 2001-2003 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Lake Snell Perry and Associates - Perry (20000132) - Child Health and Medicaid, 2000-2001 (Box 103, Folder 1-2)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Guyer (20030196) - Healthy Steps National Evaluation, 2002-2005 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - UCLA - Schuster (20020750) - Preventive Healthcare for Children, 2002-2004 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Lake Snell Perry and Associates - Perry (20030085) - Transition from Disaster Relief Medicaid to Permanent Health Coverage, 2002-2003 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Lake Snell Perry and Associates - Perry (20030085) - Focus Group Transcripts (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University - Rosenberg (20020437) - Evaluating Health Pass, 2002-2003 (Box 104, Folder 3-4)
  - Georgetown University - Kofman (20040610) - Discount Health Plans, 2004-2005 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Oregon Health Policy and Research - Smith (20040741) - Impact of Program Changes, Oregon Health Plan, 2004-2005 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Georgetown University - Pollitz (20020719) - The Needs of Chronically Ill People in Private Insurance Markets, 2002-2005 (Box 105, Folder 2-4)
  - Columbia University - Mailman (20010647) - Task Force on Health Insurance, 2001-2003 (Box 105, Folder 5-6)
  - Columbia University - Mailman (20010647) - Task Force on Health Insurance, 2001-2003 (Box 106, Folder 1-2)
  - Mathematica Policy Research - Verdier (20020152) - Expanding Medicare Coverage for Disabled Americans, 2001-2004 (Box 106, Folder 3-6)
  - National Hispanic Medical Association (NHMA) - Reducing Health Insurance Barriers and Improving Quality of Care for Hispanic Populations, 2001-2006 (Box 107, Folder 1-2)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Vlahov (20020230) - Post Disaster Mental Health Needs Assessment (Box 107, Folder 3-5)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Vlahov (20020230) - Post Disaster Mental Health Needs Assessment (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - University of Texas, Austin - Apfel (20030188) - The Future of Health Insurance for America's Families Prospectus (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Harvard Medical School - Reede (20030377) - Women of Color as Leaders in Public Health and Health Policy (Box 108, Folder 3-5)
  - ICF, Inc. - Barth (20010115) - Healthy Steps Program Support, 2001-2002 (Box 109, Folder 1-2)
  - ICF, Inc. - Barth (20010645) - Healthy Steps Program Support, 2001-2002 (Box 109, Folder 3-5)
  - ICF, Inc. - Barth (20010645) - Healthy Steps Program Support, 2001-2003 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - ICF, Inc. - Barth (20010695) - Healthy Steps Program Support, 2002-2003 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - ICF, Inc. - Barth (20010234) - Healthy Steps Program Support, 2001-2004 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Institute for Health Care Improvement (IHI) - Berwick (20010380) - Examining the Business Case for Improving Health Care Quality, 2001-2003 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Institute for Health Care Improvement (IHI) - Berwick (20010380) - Examining the Business Case for Improving Health Care Quality - Proposal Development (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Institute for Health Care Improvement (IHI) - Berwick (20010380) - Examining the Business Case for Improving Health Care Quality - Articles and Background (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Institute for Health Care Improvement (IHI) - Berwick (20010380) - Examining the Business Case for Improving Health Care Quality - Administration and Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Institute for Health Care Improvement (IHI) - Berwick (20010380) - Examining the Business Case for Improving Health Care Quality - Grant Products, 2001-2002 (Box 111, Folder 2-3)
  - Community Service Society of New York - Molnar (20010289) - Beyond Eligibility Conference, 2000-2003 (Box 111, Folder 4-5)
  - Community Service Society of New York - Molnar (20010289) - Beyond Eligibility Conference - Grant Products, 2000-2003 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - UCLA - Halfon (980562) - Pediatric Development Project (Medicaid Child Development Services), 1998-2004 (Box 112, Folder 1-3)
  - UCLA - Halfon (980562) - Pediatric Development Project (Medicaid Child Development Services) - Grant Products (Box 112, Folder 4-5)
  - UCLA - Halfon (980562) - Pediatric Development Project (Medicaid Child Development Services) - Grant Products (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - University of Kentucky - Scutchfield (20020507) - Assessing Information Needs for A Quality Patient-Centered Referral (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - University of Kentucky - Scutchfield (20020507) - Assessing Information Needs for A Quality Patient-Centered Referral - Proposal Development, 2001-2002 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - University of Kentucky - Scutchfield (20020507) - Assessing Information Needs for A Quality Patient-Centered Referral (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - University of Kentucky - Scutchfield (20020507) - Assessing Information Needs for A Quality Patient-Centered Referral - Grant Products, 2002-2004 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - University of Kentucky - Scutchfield (20020507) - Assessing Information Needs for A Quality Patient-Centered Referral - Grant Products, 2002-2005 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - ICF, Inc. - Barth (20010645) - Healthy Steps Program Support - Grant Products, 2002 (Box 114, Folder 2-3)
  - ICF, Inc. - Barth (20010645) - Healthy Steps Program Support - Grant Products, 2001-2002 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Georgetown University - Feder (980205) - Long-Term Care Program Direction - Grant Products, 1998-2000 (Box 115, Folder 2-5)
  - Georgetown University - Feder (980205) - Long-Term Care Program Direction - Grant Products, 1999-2000 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Georgetown University - Feder (980205) - Long-Term Care Program Direction, 1997-2000 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Georgetown University - Feder (970273) - Frail Elders Program Direction, Year Three - Administration, 2000 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Georgetown University - Feder (970273) - Frail Elders Program Direction, Year Three - Grant Products, 1997-1998 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Georgetown University - Feder (970273) - Frail Elders Program Direction, Year Three - Administration, 1996-2000 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health (94-52) - Final Report, 2002 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Georgetown University - Feder (970273) - Frail Elders Program Direction, Year Three - Grant Products, 1996-2001 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - George Washington University - Rosenbaum (980772) - Promoting Quality Child Development Services Through Medicaid Managed Care Contracts (980772) - Administration (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - George Washington University - Rosenbaum (980772) - Promoting Quality Child Development Services Through Medicaid Managed Care Contracts (980772) - Articles and Background (Box 117, Folder 3-4)
  - Lake Snell Perry and Associates - Perry (20000132) - Focus Group with Parents of Medicaid Enrolled Children, 2000-2002 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Lake Snell Perry and Associates - Perry (20000132) - Focus Group with Parents of Medicaid Enrolled Children - Grant Products (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Lake Snell Perry and Associates - Perry (20000132) - Focus Group with Parents of Medicaid Enrolled Children - Proposal Development, 1999-2000 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - State of Washington (20010465) - ABCD Project - Building State Child Development Services - Administration, 2001-2002 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - State of Washington (20010465) - ABCD Project - Building State Child Development Services - Grant Products, 2000-2001 (Box 118, Folder 4-5)
  - State of Washington (20010465) - ABCD Project - Building State Child Development Services - Proposal Development (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - State of Washington (20010465) - ABCD Project - Building State Child Development Services - Proposal Development (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - State of Washington (20010465) - ABCD Project - Building State Child Development Services - Correspondence (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Johns Hopkins University (20010063) - Healthy Steps National Evaluation - Proposal, 2000 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Johns Hopkins University (20010063) - Healthy Steps National Evaluation - Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Johns Hopkins University (20010063) - Healthy Steps National Evaluation - Administration, 2000-2002 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Johns Hopkins University (20010063) - Healthy Steps National Evaluation - Grant Products, 2001-2002 (Box 119, Folder 6-7)
  - UCLA (970654) - Healthy Steps Parent Survey - Proposal and Administration, 1997-2002 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - UCLA (970654) - Healthy Steps Parent Survey - Grant Products, 1997-2000 (Box 120, Folder 2-3)
  - National Committee for Quality Assurance (NCQA) - Paulson (20010099) - Developing Patient-Centered Measures of Physician Quality, 2000-2003 (Box 120, Folder 4-5)
  - National Committee for Quality Assurance (NCQA) - Paulson (20010099) - Developing Patient-Centered Measures of Physician Quality, 2001-2003 (Box 121, Folder 1-4)
  - National Committee for Quality Assurance (NCQA) - Paulson (20010099) - Developing Patient-Centered Measures of Physician Quality (Box 122, Folder 1-2)
  - Columbia University - Klitzman (20000356), 1999-2002 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - New York University (NYU) - Boufford (20010031), 2000-2002 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - Leape (990557) - Physician and Medical Error, 1999-2001 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - American Association of Health Plans (AAHP) - Bocchino (990469), 1998-1999 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - American Association of Health Plans (AAHP) - Bocchino (990469), 1998-1999 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Bachrach (20020287) - Health Coverage for Immigrants in New York State, 2001-2002 (Box 123, Folder 2-3)
  - New York University (NYU) - Boufford (20020375) - Health Care in New York: A New Leadership Briefing (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Primary Care Development Corp. - Boyce (20040753) - Learning Collaborative Planning Project, 2003-2005 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Wellspring Innovative Solutions - Kehoe (20020653), 2001-2004 (Box 124, Folder 1-2)
  - Physicians for Human Rights - Rubenstein (20000539) (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Physicians for Human Rights - Rubenstein (20000539) - Correspondence (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Stanford University - Monsen (20000390), 1998-2003 (Box 124, Folder 5)